<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contract>

    <title>
        Sample of a contract
    </title>

    <subtitle>
        This is a subtitle
    </subtitle>

    <body>

        <title>Interpretations</title>

        <item-with-children marker-type="disc">
            <item>In these Articles:</item>

            <child-item>
                <item>**“Address”** means a postal address or, for the purposes of electronic communication, a
                    fax number, email address or telephone number for receiving text messages;</item>
            </child-item>

            <child-item>
                <item>
                    **“Articles”** means the Company’s articles of association;
                </item>
            </child-item>

            <item>
                And that concludes the definitions.
            </item>
        </item-with-children>

        <item>
            Unless the context requires otherwise, other words or expressions contained in these Articles bear
            the same meaning as in the Companies Act 2006 as in force on the date when these Articles become
            binding on the Co-operative.
            Schedule 1 to the Companies (Model Articles) Regulations 2008 shall apply to the Co-operative, save
            where amended or replaced by these Articles.
            In the case of any variation or inconsistency between these Articles and the model articles, these
            Articles shall prevail.
        </item>

        <title>Offer of shares and debentures</title>

        <item>
            The Co-operative is a private company and accordingly shall not offer to the public any type of shares
            in or debentures of the Co-operative nor shall it allot or agree to allot such shares or debentures
            with a view to their being offered for sale to the public.
        </item>

        <title>Resolutions</title>


        <item-with-children marker-type="loweralpha">
            <item>Decisions at general meetings shall be made by passing resolutions:</item>

            <child-item>
                <item>Decisions involving an alteration to articles that have been Entrenched in accordance with
                    section 22 of the Act require the approval of 100% of the Members.</item>
            </child-item>

            <child-item>
                <item-with-children marker-type="lowerroman">
                    <item>
                        The following decisions must be made by special resolution:
                    </item>
                    <child-item>
                        <item>
                            Decisions involving an alteration to the Articles of the Co-operative, except where an
                            article is Entrenched as detailed above;
                        </item>
                    </child-item>
                    <child-item>
                        <item>
                           Decisions to expel Members;
                        </item>
                    </child-item>
                    <child-item>
                        <item>
                            Decisions to dispose of assets of the Co-operative equivalent in value to one-third of the
                            Co-operative’s last published balance sheet, as detailed in these Articles;
                        </item>
                    </child-item>
                    <child-item>
                        <item>
                            The decision to wind up the Co-operative;
                        </item>
                    </child-item>
                    <child-item>
                        <item>
                            Other decisions which are required so by statute.
                        </item>
                    </child-item>
                </item-with-children>
            </child-item>


            <child-item>
                <item>All other decisions shall be made by ordinary resolution.</item>
            </child-item>
        </item-with-children>

    </body>


</contract>